Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, photograph albums documenting life at Yale
1912-1916
RU 657
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(6 boxes)
The collection consists of five photograph albums compiled by Walter Jackson Freeman while a student at Yale College, 1912-1916. Highlights of the collection are the photographs of sports at Yale, most specifically crew, football, track, and baseball. Included are pictures of home and away games, as well as tours to various parts of the country. The albums also contain many photographs of the activities of societies and fraternities, including tapping, hazing, and heeling. Each photograph is identified in the author's handwriting, and the caption information is included in the inventory. The albums provide a comprehensive image of student life at Yale during the early part of the twentieth-century.
Freeman, Walter, 1895-1972
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
The albums are very fragile. Patrons must consult photocopies in Box 6 before requesting originals.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of five photograph albums compiled by Walter Jackson Freeman while a student at Yale College, 1912-1916. Highlights of the collection are the photographs of sports at Yale, most specifically crew, football, track, and baseball. Included are pictures of home and away games, as well as tours to various parts of the country. The albums also contain many photographs of the activities of societies and fraternities, including tapping, hazing, and heeling. Each photograph is identified in the author's handwriting, and the caption information is included in the inventory. The albums provide a comprehensive image of student life at Yale during the early part of the twentieth-century.
Arrangement
Arranged by volume number.
Photographs; Freeman, Walter, 1895-1972; Yale University -- Baseball; Yale University -- Football; Yale University -- Rowing; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University -- Track and field
- Volumes I and II
  Conditions Governing Access
  The albums are very fragile. Patrons must consult photocopies in Box 6 before requesting originals.
  - Page 3
    - 1. Sophomore baseball, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3. Yale Harvard -- Gales Ferry, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 4. Harvard Yard (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Page 4
    - 5. Country Fire, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6. Second crew, 1916 (Pratt-Fox-Newton) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 7. Sturtevant-Sheffield, Nichalls, Gianini (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 8. New Haven Yards (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Page 5
    - 9. Henley regatta (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 10. Punting (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 11. Sailor on the harbor (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 12. [Henley regatta] (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 13. [Punting] (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 14. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 15. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 16. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 17. Bunker, Shepard, Manie, Goodlek, Phoenix (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Page 6
    - 18. A traffic hold up on Elm Street (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 19. Fun at Williams (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 20. Digging foundations for new Bones Building, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 21. University of Illinois (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 22. Advertising convict ship --Success, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 23. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 24. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 25. Jim Donnally (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Page 7
    - 26-27. [Crew] (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 28. Graduates at the spring regatta, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 29. Itor, Thompson, Stern, Smith, Bissell, Chisolm, Emerson, Shore, Caldwell (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Page 8
    - 30. Lahr, Thompson, Gee, Levy, White, Aldrich, Gary, Ecman, Caldwell - Oval, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 31. Yale 2nd trying out on the Schuylkill, Easter, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 32. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 33. Guy Vickalls (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Page 9
    - 34. Start of Dramat trip - Christmas, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 35. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 - Lyman (3rdfrom Left) Tittman (2ndfrom right - wounded Aug 1918), Guernsey (right) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 36. 1916 Freshman Squad: Standing, Johnson, Walsh, Gurney, Aldrich, Walsh, White, Potter; Seated - Wells, Shepard, Wilcox, Arnold, Rumelin, Graves, Vaughn (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 37. Bowl entrance (under construction) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 38. [crew] (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 39. Taft reception, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Page 10
    - 40. [Baseball] (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 41. Moon courted by Jupiter over old Library, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 42. Spring meet [track], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 43. Treasure Chest chorus (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 44. Yale Penn. [baseball] - Burdett 1914S catcher (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Page 11
    - 45. Potter - Hadley (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 46. James, D. Stewart, Oler - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 47. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 48. Handy (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 49. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Page 12
    - 50. [winter storm] (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 51. Levy, Williams, Mikell, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 52. Kimberly drills Booth, Graves, Taylor, Hapwood, Eckman, Crocker - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 53. Alumni Day, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Page 13
    - 54-57. Milford Wreck, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Page 14
    - 58. Vaughn, Way - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 59. Milford Wreck, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 60. Milford Wreck, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 61. Ricketts, Lewis, Cady, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 62. Building Shubert Theatre, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Page 15
    - 63. West Point Cadets visit Yale, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 64. Mulqueen, J. Stewart, Walsh, Campbell (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 65. [bulldog - Handsome Dan (?)] (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 66. Berkeley Oval (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 67. [Spring fun] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Page 16
    - 68. Circus, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 69. Yale Hope Mission men clear pavement (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 70. Colgate scores on Yale [football], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 71. 1914 resurrects Diabolo (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 72. [Spring fun] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Page 17
    - 73. Hockey Squad passing Edwards (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 74. Spinning tops (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 75. Lock step at Princeton (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 76. Behind the scenes at Commons (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 77. Whiting, Williams, Rabold, Williams, John Whiting Quartet (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 78. Thanksgiving Party in Dwight (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 79. [Group masqueraded on coach] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 80. [Man masqueraded on coach] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 81. 1914 Omega Lambda Chi Tussle (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Page 18
    - 82. Jim Donnally and Co-op clerks, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 83. C.J. Coe testing model of fliers, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 84. Pat, Woodbine, Farr at the tape [track] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 85. Winter campus by night (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 86. Elephants in circus parade (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 87. Omega Lambda Chi Bicycle Polo, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 88. Senior party to Mamauguin, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 89. [dining - with young boys] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 90. [duplicate of photo 72] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Page 19
    - 91. K. Woolley, Y 1917 takes subscriptions for the News, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 92. F. Couch Y 1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 93. Iphigenia (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 94. Iphigenia (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Page 20
    - 95. 1914 Class party - Ketcham (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 96. 1914 in Costume (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 97. Welch, Baber - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 98. [Runners] (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 99. Teaching English in Byers (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Page 21
    - 100. [Group of ladies and men outside door of 181?? Street] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 101. [Crew] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 102. Eastman, Phoenix, Shore, Tharr (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 103. Red, Burnet (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 104. Busy Day at crew, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 105. [Iphigenia] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Page 22
    - 106. Lewis L. Bredin, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 107. [Iphigenia] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 108. [Iphigenia] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 109. [Band Stand with Carriage] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Page 23
    - 110. Oler, 1915 [high jump] (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 111. Howe, Putnam, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 112. Achelis, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 114. [Man outside building] (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 115. Dean Fred Jones reading in a library (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Page 24
    - 116. 1914 - Overton, Cretiore (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 117. Overton, 1916 (Killed at Chateau Thierry, July 19, 1918) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 118. Denegre, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 119. Hampton, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 120. 1916 Hockey team, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 121. [Man outside building] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Page 25
    - 122. Neave [in military uniform] (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 123. 1913 Sheff monthly board (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 124. Davidson, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 125. 1913 [group outside building] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Page 26
    - 126. 1915 Decennial (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 127. Eckman, Burnett, Ricketts - Hampton on Crocker (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 128. Preparedness, 1915 - Hopgood, Booth, Graves, Taylor, Eckman, Crocker, Kimberly (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 129. Waiting in line for tickets, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 130. 1916 in 1915 [on fence] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Page 27
    - 131. New Haven Harbor [sailboat] (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 132. Yale-Princeton [football], 1913 - Baker downed (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 133. Kimberley [with sword] (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 134. Crocker, Proctor [playing marbles] (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 135. West Point Cadets (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 136. Vaughn, Gould [sitting on curb] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Page 29
    - 142. Rushing - 1917 Sophomores (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 143. Arlington Museum (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 144. Grand Theatre after the fire (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 145. Arlington Museum (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Page 30
    - 146. Tighe (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 147. Church and Chapel [street corner] (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 148. Boardman, Bassett, Platt (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 149. Balloon Corps in Hartford, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 150. James, Hapgood, Miller, Eckman, Taylor Graves, Crocker, Burnett [on march] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Page 31
    - 151. Balloon Study, 1916 [close up of gondola] (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 152. Balloon Study, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 153. Alumni Day, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 154. Omega Lambda Chi, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 155. Gambardella (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Page 32
    - 156. Shellman, Bissell, Williams - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 157. James, Fitts, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 158. [duplicate of picture 150] (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 159. Field Gun in Cage (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 160. Baker [in room] (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 161. Hopgood (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Page 28
      - 137. Chism, 1913 [gymnastics] (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 138. Cloister, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 139. Yale-Princeton [Baseball], 1914 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 140. The Charge - Booth, Taylor, Eckman, Graves, Kimberley (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 141. [West Point Cadets and Grads on Old Campus] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Page 33
    - 162. Battery Practice, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 163. Movie directors, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 164. [Battery Practice, 1916] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 165. Omega Lambda Chi Spectators [old campus] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 166. War map in library hall, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 162. Battery Practice, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 163. Movie directors, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 164. [Battery Practice, 1916] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 165. Omega Lambda Chi Spectators [old campus] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 166. War map in library hall, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Page 34
    - 167. William Phelps, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 168. [Fixing auto - Handsome Dan (?) Watching] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 169. Danford [in uniform], 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 170. [Balloon Study] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Page 35
    - 171. Vreeland 1912S, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 172. Bab Sheffield, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 173. Ketcham and Avery lead the team on the field,Yale-Princeton [football], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 174. Whiting Quartet, 1914 (see picture 77) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 175. After a muddy half, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 176. Denegre as Jack Johnson, Omega Lambda Chi,1915 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Page 36
    - 177. Cunningham, 1914 [tennis] (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 178. Parade to Brown Game, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 179. Crew Parade, 1914 [Wall Street] (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 180. Tree surgery (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 181. Old bowling alley, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Page 37
    - 182. Early game, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 183. [Phelps Hall from Green in rain] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 184. [Through a gate to old campus] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 185. Freshmen Crew, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 186. [Parade on College Street in front of Byers Hall in rain] (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Page 38
    - 187. [Field hockey in front of bowl] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 188. Samuels, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 189. Tom Lewis (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 190. Lake Whitney, 1914 [hockey and skating] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 191. Lake Whitney, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Page 39
    - 192. Wright Hall, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 193. Keys - Saint Anthony, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 194. 1913 (see picture 125) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 195. Rain, 1913 (see picture 183) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 196. Fraternity campaign, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 197. 1915 Record board - Hazard, Tuttle, Jutte, Hatch, Boomer (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Page 40
    - 198-201. Class reunions, June 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Page 41
    - 202. A.N.S. Jackson - English runner, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 203. R.N. Williams, 1915 [tennis] (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 204. 163 Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 205. Young man in a sailboat (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 206. E. Sheldon 1916S [football] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Page 42
    - 207. Enwright, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 208. Gun team, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 209. Stewart (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 210. Eastman, Hoff, Proctor, Sutherland, Welch, Jones, Polhamus - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 211. Reeve, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 212. [Brush fire] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Page 43
    - 213. Sophomore baseball, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 214. Dash practice, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 215. Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 216. Shepard (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 217. G.E. Brown 1915S (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Page 44
    - 218. Whitney, Dartmouth at Penn - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 219. Church, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 220. Polhamus, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 221. Princeton, being photographed (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 222. Yale Station [at Berkeley Oval] (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Page 45
    - 223-24. 1913 [football] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 225. 1913 Yale versus Maine [football] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 226. Tad Jones, Vonholt, Marting, Catlin (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 227. Jones (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 228. [Football] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 229. [Football practice] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 230. Coaney [tackle practice] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Page 46
    - 231. Frosh vs. Andover [football] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 232. [Football practice] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 233. [Football] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 234. Yale at Princeton [football], 1912 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 235. Smoothing the turf (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 236. [Football, not at Bowl] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 237. [Football practice at Bowl] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Page 47
    - 238. Gianini, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 239. New London, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 240. First Crew, March 1916 (1 neg.) (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 241. View from Osborn [into Old Campus] (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Page 48
    - 242. Nickalls (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 243. [Launching a shell] (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 244. 1915 Crew - Morse, Wiman, Meyer, Sturtevant, Sheldon, Law, Bennit, McLane (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 245. 1915 [at Berkeley Oval Gate in auto] Ricketts, Kalhmann, Crocker, Phenix, Polhmaus, Perry, Hampton, Porter (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Page 49
    - 246. 1844 Crew [parody] (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 247. [Crew at floating dock] (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 248. Duplicate of picture 246 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 249. Coaching launch at Penn. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 250. After a hail storm, 1915 [tree down in front of Connecticut Hall] (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Page 50
    - 251. McLane, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 252. Welch, Jones, Putnam, Gardner, Emerson, Lewis, Bowden - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 253. 1913 at play (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 254. [Crew at practice] (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Page 51
    - 255. Country fire, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 256. 1914 - Harbison, Carrington, Goodlet, Frank (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 257. Penn Crew - Easter, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 258. 1915 [a march] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Page 52
    - 259. Burnet, Walsh, Mulqueen, Burgess, Crocker (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 260. [Crew at practice] (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 261. [Crew at practice] (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 262. [Young man sitting on steps] (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 263. A. Munsun, 1913 [crew] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Page 53
    - 264. 1916 - Offett, Farwell [hurdle jumping] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 265. Johnstone [pole vaulting] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 266. Alumni Day, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 267. University of Pennsylvania (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 268. Mack, Wagoner [Pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 269. Osborn Lab Tower [under construction] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 270. 1915 [within Berkeley Oval] (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Page 54
    - 271. Teschner beats Treadway, 1915 [track] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 272. Treadway (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 273. Freshmen track squad, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 274. Orr, Walker - Interscholastics, 1914 [track] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 275. Movie men, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Page 55
    - 276. Barron wins mile relay at Penn, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 277. Rosener ex Y 1916 - 1913 [hurdle] (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 278. News heelers bicycle polo - Omega Lambda Chi (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 279. Buck at Penn, 1914 [pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 280. [Team member - track] (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 281. Roos, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 282. Hampton, 1915 [broad jump] (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Page 56
    - 283. [Pole vaulter] (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 284. Oler, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 285. Putnam, 1916 [running] (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 286. Gifford, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 287. Munsen, Caldwell, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Page 57
    - 288. Ricketts, Treadway, Cowles - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 289. Ricketts, Treadway, Cornell - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 290. McKenzie wins 2 mile relay at Penn., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 291. Photographic battery - Penn relays, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 292. Wilkie (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 293. Hatch and Loreman (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 294. Spring track meet, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 295. Carter [pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 296. R.A. Douglas, 1914 [pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 297. Buck (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 298. A. Munson, A. Jones, W. Porter, Howe, Atter, C. Munson [sailing], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 299. Worm pounding, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 300. Douglas at Penn, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Page 59
    - 301. Track and Field Practice (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 302. Sigma Delta Psi trials (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 303. Longstretch [gymnastics], 1916 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 304. [Old Campus toward Battell] (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 305. Crowell (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 306. Water fight [in front of Oval], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Page 60
    - 307. Sigma Delta Psi trials (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 308. Kelly [hurdles], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 309. Lacrosse [outside bowl] (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 310. Maximius, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 311. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 312. Dean Jones (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Page 61
    - 313. Hand spring trials (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 314. Baldridge winning for Yale against Harvard (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - wrestling?, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 315. Heavyweight match [Wrestling], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 316. Fraternity campaign, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Page 62
    - 317. Overton [track] (1 neg.), 1914 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 318. Taft corner [Chapel and College Streets - Winter], 1912 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 319. Davis [hurdles], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 320. [Man on threshold] (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 321. Kite time on Phelps [roof] (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Page 63
    - 322. Vanderbilt court (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 323. Cornell Y 1915, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 324. Giving the crew a send off, 1913 - Harper Y 1913 leading (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 325. Dancing lesson by Johnny Mack, Mack, Bunker, Carter (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 326. Johnstone 1914S (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Page 64
    - 327. Osborn Laboratories, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 328. Roos [shot put], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 329. Potter 1914S, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 330. Porter, Shephard, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 331. Dwight, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 332. Circus Parade [Elm Street], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Page 65
    - 333. Indoor Track (1 neg.), 1916 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 334. Elkin after the prom, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 335. Torson, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 336. Library gate (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 337. Newstetter - Penn [pole vault], 1915 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Page 66
    - 338. Matthews, Carter [pole vault], 1914 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 339. Levy, Bassett, Aldrich, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 340. Bowling alleys, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 341. Johnstone [pole vault], 1914 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 342. [Group in Berkeley Oval] (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 343. Stafford Y 1914, [conducting in a church] (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Page 67
    - 344. Boathouse at Gales Ferry, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 345. 1916 Delta Kappa Epsilon crew: Pratt, Rinehart, Guernsey, Roberts, Wilson, Otis, Titus, Black (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 346. 1914 [Circus Parade - Elm Street] (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 347. [Laundry Lady - looking East toward Ott Library] (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Page 68
    - 348. Yale beats Penn - Easter, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 349. Starting Second - Sprool, Toole, Wilson, Allen, Johnstone - Hoopt (died in Italy, 1918), Robinson (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 350. Watching little boys fight in Berkeley Oval (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 351. [Crew in shell] (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Page 69
    - 352. Baseball Team - Reilly, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 353. Taft, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 354. Reckendorfer [baseball], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 355. 1915 [at railroad station] (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 356. [A mess] (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Page 70
    - 357. Hitched for 3-legged race, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 358. Freshman mandolin club, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 359. Wright gateway (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 360. Delta Kappa Epsilon team - Fagan, Coates, Roberts, S. Miller, Howes, Dickey (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 361. Yale movies, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 362. Reilly misses plate in slide for home - Penn, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Page 71
    - 363. Zeta psi team, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 35)